Guide to the Institute for Independent Education records, 1984-2005.
Institute for Independent Education records, 1984-2005
- Series II. Activities of the Institute for Independent Education 1984-2004
  - Projects: Meeting College and Employment Needs, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Projects: Meeting College and Employment Needs, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Projects: Capacity Building and Leadership at Independent Neighborhood Schools, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Projects: Increasing the Leadership Capacity of Independent Community-Based Schools, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Expanded guide to the archives of the Institute For Independent Education, Inc., 2005 (Box 9)
- Series III. Photographic Archives
  - Photographic Archives (Overview) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Group 1: School Buildings (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Group 2: Math Alive! Teacher Development Program, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Group 3: Math Alive! Follow-up Workshops and Visits to Schools, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Group 4: Excellence in Baltimore Independent School Program, Writing & Art Contest, and Visits to Schools, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Group 5: Excellence in Baltimore Independent Schools, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Group 6: Visits to Schools, Academic Competition in Black History Program, and Sarafina! at the Kennedy Center, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Group 7: Africa and the World Newspaper and a Capital Hill Reception for Delegates from the Congressional Black Caucus, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Group 8: Network Planning Committee, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Group 9: Southeast, Northeast & Midwest Regional Conferences, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Group 10: Accreditation Visit to Greenforest Christian Academy; 10th Anniversary Conference & Awards Dinner, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Group 11: Second National Conference, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Group 12: Orientation to Accreditation Seminar; Network Strategy Meeting; Third National Conference, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Group 13: Mathematics Curricula Workshop; Orientation to Accreditation, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Group 14: Mathematics Curricula Workshop; Cush Campus Schools Library, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Group 15: School Choice Outreach; Cyberspace Competition and Marcus Garvey School Conference; Visit to West Angeles Christian Academy, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Group 16: Undated Visits to Schools (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Group 17: Undated School Founders and School Principals (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Series IV. Corporate History of the Institute
  - Minutes of the Board of Directors, 1985-2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Defining and Defending the Institute's Philosophy, Mission & Programs, 1985-1996 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Expressions of Interest in the Work of the Institute, 1986-1994 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Series V. Secondary Sources
  - African-American Schools: Unpublished Manuscripts, 1975-2003 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - African-American Schools: Unpublished Manuscripts, 1986-2001 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Transcripts of Interviews with African-American Educators, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Transcripts of Interviews with African-American Educators, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Commentary on Trends in Education, Philosophy, & Research (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - African-American History (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Prominent African-Americans (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Curricular Issues (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Education of African-Americans (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Education of African-Americans (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - African-American Independent Schools (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - African-American Independent Schools (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - African-American Independent Schools (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - African-American Education & Enrichment Programs: Contemporary Sources (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - African-American Education & Enrichment Programs: Historical Sources (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - African-American Education & Enrichment Programs: Historical Sources (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - African-American Education & Enrichment Programs: Historical Sources (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - African-American Education & Enrichment Programs: Historical Sources (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - African-American Education & Enrichment Programs: Historical Sources (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - African-American Education & Enrichment Programs: Historical Sources (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - African-American Education & Enrichment Programs: Historical Sources (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - African-American Education & Enrichment Programs: Historical Sources (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Dr. John Henrik Clarke Materials (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Dr. John Henrik Clarke Materials (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Series VI. Institute Publications
  - Institute Publications, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Institute Publications, 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Institute Publications, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Institute Publications, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Institute Publications, 1993-1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Institute Publications, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Series VII. Financial Records
  - Audited Financial Statements, 1985-2002 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Financial Statements, December 31, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Financial Statements, December 31, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements, December 31, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements, December 31, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Audited Financial Statements, December 31, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements, December 31, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements, December 31, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements, December 31, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements (With Independent Auditor's Report Thereon), December 31, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements (With Independent Auditor's Report Thereon), December 31, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements (With Independent Auditor's Report Thereon), December 31, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements (With Independent Auditor's Report Thereon), December 31, 1996 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements (With Independent Auditor's Report Thereon), December 31, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements (With Independent Auditor's Report Thereon), December 31, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements (With Independent Auditor's Report Thereon), December 31, 1999 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements (With Independent Auditor's Report Thereon), December 31, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements (With Independent Auditor's Report Thereon), December 31, 2001 (Box 8)
  - Institute For Independent Education, Inc. Audited Financial Statements (With Independent Auditor's Report Thereon), December 31, 2002 (Box 8)